<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Projects on LGM</title><link>https://csmertx.github.io/Blog/stuff/</link><description>Recent content in Projects on LGM</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><atom:link href="https://csmertx.github.io/Blog/stuff/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Paint Holder</title><link>https://csmertx.github.io/Blog/stuff/2023/modelpaintholder/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://csmertx.github.io/Blog/stuff/2023/modelpaintholder/</guid><description>January 20, 2023 Created: 04-16-22 I made a paint holder out of epoxy sculpt that secured the little 0.25oz/7.4ml square bottles. Switching out bottles was a chore due to the finish and design. So I made this with Fusion 360 to alleviate those gripes. Unfortunately, I never included bolt threading in the design due to a non-existent time crunch. This might seem like overkill, but I&amp;rsquo;d rather spend this amount on something to hold the paint than to replace carpet(s).</description></item><item><title>Pen Cup</title><link>https://csmertx.github.io/Blog/stuff/2023/pencup/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://csmertx.github.io/Blog/stuff/2023/pencup/</guid><description>January 20, 2023 Created: 03-10-22 One of my guilty pleasure hobbies is skateboarding with my fingers. I was never average at skateboarding and Florida has a lot of summer rain. Anyway, I wanted my desk to look nicer, and so I made this thing. Used silver Testors model paint for the sign.
STL Download
Quarter Pipe Pen Organizer Printed via hubs.com
SLA Prototype gray filament (FDM) ~$100 (Large print 200x90x120mm, 200μm layer height) Glass top bumpers (rubber pads) for those curious are 10x50x2mm by GINOYA</description></item><item><title>RPi4 Console</title><link>https://csmertx.github.io/Blog/stuff/2023/rpi4console/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://csmertx.github.io/Blog/stuff/2023/rpi4console/</guid><description>January 20, 2023 Created: 06-07-21 RPi4 == Raspberry Pi 4
I wanted a tiny console to check out ARM architecture stuff. My notes are at: Linux &amp;gt; Devices &amp;gt; RPi4
This one does not include a parts list because this configuration killed the official RPi4 LCD screen. I sold my RPi4 because of sketchy hats (addon boards). Next attempt will be something different (if there is another attempt).</description></item><item><title>Wrist Rests</title><link>https://csmertx.github.io/Blog/stuff/2023/silicone_wrist_rests/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://csmertx.github.io/Blog/stuff/2023/silicone_wrist_rests/</guid><description>January 20, 2023 Created: 03-03-20 I&amp;rsquo;ll try my best to keep these posts to the point and to not go crazy with the details. At the end of 2020 I stumbled in to some remote contract work. This job required the use of a keyboard, and a lot of typing. Instead of spending time and money on future RSI surgeries, I decided to get an urklenomic keyboard. The problem with the keyboard I bought (aside from the price tag) was that my wrists would go numb after four hours.</description></item></channel></rss>