<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>2022 on CSx</title><link>https://csmertx.github.io/Blog/daynight/2022/</link><description>Recent content in 2022 on CSx</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><atom:link href="https://csmertx.github.io/Blog/daynight/2022/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>08-22</title><link>https://csmertx.github.io/Blog/daynight/2022/0822/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://csmertx.github.io/Blog/daynight/2022/0822/</guid><description>August 9, 2022 My wildling side. In the grand scheme of things, this wasn&amp;rsquo;t that long ago August 11, 2022 The day a soccer goal chose violence August 9, 2022 My wildling side. In the grand scheme of things, this wasn&amp;rsquo;t that long ago The mobile home still visible to the left of the red and gray building was where I lived with my folks from 1997-2001.
My folks lost their home in Hawthorne, FL (where I learned to respect nature 1989-1996&amp;ndash;snakes), and moved to Gainesville, FL.</description></item><item><title>09-22</title><link>https://csmertx.github.io/Blog/daynight/2022/0922/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://csmertx.github.io/Blog/daynight/2022/0922/</guid><description>September 1, 2022 RIP Spider-man. You were loved. September 5, 2022 Coupé de ville September 6, 2022 High school drafting class. This one hurt my psyche quite a bit September 8, 2022 From when I worked at United Tote September 18, 2022 Too ambitious to be a bench warmer September 1, 2022 RIP Spider-man. You were loved. This story required a separate post. Something I had to get out. My first grade bus driver Mr.</description></item><item><title>10-22</title><link>https://csmertx.github.io/Blog/daynight/2022/1022/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://csmertx.github.io/Blog/daynight/2022/1022/</guid><description>Oct. 28, 2022 How I learned to shovel, and why working sucks Oct. 28, 2022 How I learned to shovel, and why working sucks I started my first job at the age of seven. Our family dog (black labrador) had a litter of puppies, and I was tasked to care for them (which included shoveling). So, for a few months I moved around dog food, filled bowls, and crawled into the makeshift puppy kennel in our backyard to complete my daily waste extraction quest.</description></item><item><title>11-22</title><link>https://csmertx.github.io/Blog/daynight/2022/1122/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://csmertx.github.io/Blog/daynight/2022/1122/</guid><description>Nov. 4, 2022 Mana from U-Store-It Nov. 4, 2022 Mana from U-Store-It The time period created a movie known as Office Space. It was a time of great technological upheaval, and a time of great technological waste. Many were upgrading to new systems, including private and public schools. Trent Reznor was one of the newest musical talents to have music videos, Quake the computer game had only been out a few years, and Intel Pentium II &amp;amp; III machines were tossed away in favor of laptops and more portable desktop computers.</description></item></channel></rss>