<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>2023 on CSx</title><link>https://csmertx.github.io/Blog/music/2023/</link><description>Recent content in 2023 on CSx</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><atom:link href="https://csmertx.github.io/Blog/music/2023/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Songs | 01/23</title><link>https://csmertx.github.io/Blog/music/2023/0123/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://csmertx.github.io/Blog/music/2023/0123/</guid><description>January 9, 2023 Evil Nine - They Live (They Live!) The White Stripes - The Hardest Button To Button (Elephant) Thrice - For Miles (Vheissu) Ratatat - Sunblocks (LP4) January 11, 2023 Ratatat - Mirando (Official Video) (LP3) January 12, 2023 Darren Korb - Slinger&amp;rsquo;s Song (Bastion Soundtrack) January 13, 2023 Dj Egadz - Attic (We Want Neutrinos) Beastie Boys - Triple Trouble (To The 5 Boroughs) Trans-Siberian Orchestra - Wizards in Winter (The Lost Christmas Eve) Hiroshi Kawaguchi - Main Theme (Arranged) S.</description></item><item><title>Songs | 02/23</title><link>https://csmertx.github.io/Blog/music/2023/0223/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://csmertx.github.io/Blog/music/2023/0223/</guid><description>February 02, 2023 Rooney - Sleep Song (Calling The World) Q Lazzarus- Goodbye Horses (Marc Johnson - Fully Flared) (Goodbye Horses) Fischerspooner - All We Are (Marc Johnson - Fully Flared) (Odyssey) She Wants Revenge - Us (Marc Johnson - Fully Flared) (She Wants Revenge) Aesop Rock - All Day (Nike+ ORIGINAL RUN) February 3, 2023 Ratatat - Beat 6 (9 Beats) Danny Brown - 25 Bucks ft. Purity Ring (Official Video) (Old) [NSFW] February 8, 2023 Blockhead - Gilgamesh (Dour Candy Instrumentals) February 9, 2023 R.</description></item><item><title>Songs | 03/23</title><link>https://csmertx.github.io/Blog/music/2023/0323/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://csmertx.github.io/Blog/music/2023/0323/</guid><description>March 07, 2023 Lazy Sunday - Official Sound Studio (cats.are.g0d) March 11, 2023 Runaway Horses - 56k Modem Vibing (Official Video) (YouTube) March 14, 2023 Ratatat - Seventeen Years (Unofficial Video) (Ratatat) March 31, 2023 Pink Floyd - Time (Radio Edit) (Dark Side of the Moon) March 07, 2023 Lazy Sunday - Official Sound Studio (cats.are.g0d) 🔗 Lazy Sunday - Official Sound Studio (cats.are.g0d)
Although I don&amp;rsquo;t have a TikTok account, I do understand that this song is popular on the platform.</description></item><item><title>Songs | 04/23</title><link>https://csmertx.github.io/Blog/music/2023/0423/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://csmertx.github.io/Blog/music/2023/0423/</guid><description>April 1, 2023 The Decemberists - Sons &amp;amp; Daughters (The Crane Wife) DragonForce - Through the Fire and Flames (Official Video) (Inhuman Rampage) April 8, 2023 Killswitch Engage - The End Of Heartache (Official Video) (The End Of Heartache) April 13, 2023 DragonForce - Heros Of Our Time (Official Video) (Ultra Beatdown) April 17, 2023 Guamu - Dying car alarm drops a beat (Full Version) (Guamu) April 22, 2023 Beastie Boys - Alright Hear This (Ill Communication) [NSFW] April 27, 2023 Jeff Lynne - Video!</description></item><item><title>Songs | 05/23</title><link>https://csmertx.github.io/Blog/music/2023/0523/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://csmertx.github.io/Blog/music/2023/0523/</guid><description>May 4, 2023 Ludwig Göransson - The Mandalorian (The Mandalorian: Chapter 1) May 9, 2023 AlCaHoo Radio - Stellar (AlCaHoo Radio) May 15, 2023 Death Grips - Lord of the Game ft. Mexican Girl (Leeside Skatepark Video) (Exmilitary) [NSFW] May 16, 2023 Bassnectar - Timestretch (Timestretch) May 20, 2023 Dragonforce - Reasons to Live (Ultra Beatdown) May 22, 2023 Mt. Eden - Sierra Leon (Fan Made Video) (Myspace Edition) May 28, 2023 Imagine Dragons - It&amp;rsquo;s Time (White Sea Remix) (Night Visions - 10th Anniversary Edition) May 31, 2023 Blind Guardian - At the Edge of Time (Beyond the Red Mirror) May 4, 2023 Ludwig Göransson - The Mandalorian (The Mandalorian: Chapter 1) 🔗 Ludwig Göransson - The Mandalorian (The Mandalorian: Chapter 1)</description></item><item><title>Songs | 06/23</title><link>https://csmertx.github.io/Blog/music/2023/0623/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://csmertx.github.io/Blog/music/2023/0623/</guid><description>June 1, 2023 Blind Guardian - The Throne (Beyond the Red Mirror) June 3, 2023 Blind Guardian - Distant Memories (Beyond the Red Mirror) June 9, 2023 Blind Guardian - Sacred Worlds (At the Edge of Time) June 11, 2023 Purity Ring - Obedear (Shrines) June 13, 2023 Talking Heads - Road to Nowhere (Official Video) (Little Creatures) June 25, 2023 Electric Light Orchestra (ELO) - Mr. Blue Sky (Official Video) (All Over The World) June 1, 2023 Blind Guardian - The Throne (Beyond the Red Mirror) 🔗 Blind Guardian - The Throne (Beyond the Red Mirror)</description></item><item><title>Songs | 07/23</title><link>https://csmertx.github.io/Blog/music/2023/0723/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://csmertx.github.io/Blog/music/2023/0723/</guid><description>July 13, 2023 Blind Guardian - Otherland (A Twist in the Myth) July 26, 2023 Black Box - Boss Fight (Metallic) Aesop Rock - Coveralls (Official Video) (Spirit World Field Guide) [NSFW] July 13, 2023 Blind Guardian - Otherland (A Twist in the Myth) 🔗 Blind Guardian - Otherland (A Twist in the Myth)
Also: 🔗 Live Recording of Otherland from 2008
July 26, 2023 Black Box - Boss Fight (Metallic) 🔗 Black Box - Boss Fight (Metallic)</description></item><item><title>Songs | 08/23</title><link>https://csmertx.github.io/Blog/music/2023/0823/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://csmertx.github.io/Blog/music/2023/0823/</guid><description>August 9, 2023 Blind Guardian - Time Stands Still (At The Iron Hill) (Nightfall in Middle-Earth) August 11, 2023 Kazuo Sawa, Toshiko Tasaki - Totally Rad (OST) August 13, 2023 Aesop Rock - Abandon All Hope (Music For Earthworms) (Official Video) [NSFW] Blind Guardian - Life Beyond The Spheres (The God Machine) (Official Video) August 16, 2023 Savatage - Hall Of The Mountain King (Official Music Video) (Hall Of The Mountain King) August 20, 2023 Blind Guardian - Thorn (Nightfall in Middle-Earth) August 20, 2023 Blind Guardian - Damnation (The God Machine) August 9, 2023 Blind Guardian - Time Stands Still (At The Iron Hill) (Nightfall in Middle-Earth) 🔗 Blind Guardian - Time Stands Still (At The Iron Hill) (Nightfall in Middle-Earth)</description></item><item><title>Songs | 09/23</title><link>https://csmertx.github.io/Blog/music/2023/0923/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://csmertx.github.io/Blog/music/2023/0923/</guid><description>September 1, 2023 Aesop Rock - Grace (Skelethon) [NSFW] September 2, 2023 Blind Guardian - Imaginations from the Other Side (Imaginations from the Other Side) September 13, 2023 Boards of Canada - Left Side Drive (Trans Canada Highway) September 17, 2023 Nym - Derecho ft. Emancipator (Warm Blooded Lizard) September 18, 2023 Thrice - Red Sky (LIVE) (Vheissu) Thrice - Music Box (Vheissu) September 23, 2023 Inf - The Go Round (The Go Round) September 28, 2023 DragonForce - Doomsday Party (Official Video) (Doomsday Party) September 1, 2023 Aesop Rock - Grace (Skelethon) [NSFW] 🔗 Aesop Rock - Grace (Skelethon) [NSFW]</description></item><item><title>Songs | 10/23</title><link>https://csmertx.github.io/Blog/music/2023/1023/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://csmertx.github.io/Blog/music/2023/1023/</guid><description>October 6, 2023 Green Day - Brain Stew (Official Video) (Insomniac) October 7, 2023 Gorillaz - Dare (Official Video) (Demon Days) October 14, 2023 Red Fang - Prehistoric Dog (Official Video) (Red Fang) [NSFW] October 15, 2023 True Widow - Night Witches (As High As the Highest Heavens and From the Center to the Circumference of the Earth) October 16, 2023 Jean Grae - A-Alikes (This Week) October 17, 2023 Aesop Rock - Kodokushi (Spirit World Field Guide) October 19, 2023 The Radio Dept.</description></item><item><title>Songs | 11/23</title><link>https://csmertx.github.io/Blog/music/2023/1123/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://csmertx.github.io/Blog/music/2023/1123/</guid><description>November 22, 2023 Dark Time Sunshine - Take My Hand (Official Video) (ANX) November 29, 2023 The Rosebuds - Leaves Do Fall (Birds Make Good Neighbors) November 22, 2023 Dark Time Sunshine - Take My Hand (Official Video) (ANX) 🔗 Dark Time Sunshine - Take My Hand (Official Video) (ANX)
🔗Digital includes instrumentals. Thank you
November 29, 2023 The Rosebuds - Leaves Do Fall (Birds Make Good Neighbors) 🔗 The Rosebuds - Leaves Do Fall (Birds Make Good Neighbors)</description></item><item><title>Songs | 12/23</title><link>https://csmertx.github.io/Blog/music/2023/1223/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://csmertx.github.io/Blog/music/2023/1223/</guid><description>December 1, 2023 Matchbox 20 - 3am (Official Video) (Yourself or Someone Like You) December 7, 2023 Hail Mary Mallon - Garfield (Official Video) (Are You Gonna Eat That?) Hail Mary Mallon - Meter Feeder (Official Video) (Are You Gonna Eat That?) December 23, 2023 Afroham / C Y G N - Hnstly (Chillhop Essentials Winter 2023) December 25, 2023 ØDYSSEE - Lost Memories ft. Bastien Brison (Chillhop Essentials Winter 2023) December 29, 2023 Yasper - Stay (Chillhop Essentials Winter 2023 | C2.</description></item></channel></rss>