<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Raspberry Pi 4 on Gremlin Mysteries</title><link>https://csmertx.github.io/Linux/Devices/rpi4/</link><description>Recent content in Raspberry Pi 4 on Gremlin Mysteries</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><atom:link href="https://csmertx.github.io/Linux/Devices/rpi4/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Manjaro on RPi4</title><link>https://csmertx.github.io/Linux/Devices/rpi4/manjaro/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://csmertx.github.io/Linux/Devices/rpi4/manjaro/</guid><description>Raspberry Pi 4 (2021) Waveshare WM8960 Soundcard ? Rebooting Unlike with Ubuntu 20.04, I was unable to successfully reboot the system. Why the long face? It&amp;rsquo;s not Manjaro&amp;rsquo;s fault, KDE Plasma&amp;rsquo;s onscreen (virtual) keyboard w/official 7in Pi display was (2021&amp;ndash;will revisit soon-ish) a separate hobby project. To be fair, it&amp;rsquo;s a task to get fingerprint reader working in SDDM (KDE Plasma display manager) via a 2019 Thinkpad. Since I fried my touchscreen using an off the shelf RPi power management solution, I can&amp;rsquo;t retest until I get a new display.</description></item><item><title>RetroPie on RPi4</title><link>https://csmertx.github.io/Linux/Devices/rpi4/retropie/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://csmertx.github.io/Linux/Devices/rpi4/retropie/</guid><description>Retropie on RPi4 w/Official 7in LCD &amp;amp; WM8860 soundcard First steps Installer resizes to fit the micro SD card Place games in pi/roms/&amp;lt;game_folders_of_choice&amp;gt; Place bios in pi/BIOS Access console/shell (TTY) after boot with keyboard combo: CTRL + ALT + F4 sudo raspi-config Chance localization and keyboard mapping (Localisation Options (for both)) WiFi cd Retropie-Setup sudo ./retropie_setup.sh C Configuration / Tools 843 wifi - Configure WiFi Force WiFi to use 5Ghz (if needed) check with wavemon first: wavemon sudo iwconfig wlan0 freq 5.</description></item><item><title>Ubuntu 20.04 Server 2 Desktop on RPi4</title><link>https://csmertx.github.io/Linux/Devices/rpi4/ubuntu/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://csmertx.github.io/Linux/Devices/rpi4/ubuntu/</guid><description>Ubuntu 20.04 via RPi4 w/Official 7in LCD &amp;amp; WM8860 soundcard Install Ubuntu Desktop via 20.04 Server Sign-in username: ubuntu passwword: ubuntu Change password current password: ubuntu etc. sudo dpkg-reconfigure -plow unattended-upgrades WiFi nano /etc/netplan/50-cloud-init.yaml wifis: wlan0: option: true access-points: &amp;ldquo;WiFi SSID&amp;rdquo;: password: &amp;ldquo;wifipassword&amp;rdquo; netplan apply reboot sudo apt install openssh-server wireless-tools net-tools reboot sudo apt update &amp;amp;&amp;amp; sudo apt upgrade sudo apt install libraspberrypi-bin sudo apt install aptitude neofetch tmuxinator ranger sxiv yank xsel calcurse vim powerline ubuntu-desktop sudo apt install vim-gtk3 mplayer mpv w3m-img wavemon guake barrier pi-bluetooth dosbox Kubuntu 20.</description></item></channel></rss>